export const data = [
    {
        question:' What is ReactJS?',
        option1:'Server-side framework',
        option2:'User interface framework',
        option3:'Both A and B',
        option4:'None of the above',
        answer:2,       
    },
    {
        question:'In which language is React.js written?',
        option1:'Python',
        option2:'Javascript',
        option3:'Java',
        option4:'PHP',
        answer:1,        
    },
    {
        question:'Identify the command used to create a react app.',
        option1:'npm install create-react-app',
        option2:'npm install -g create-react-app',
        option3:'install -g create-react-app',
        option4:'None of the above',
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:'The function which is called to render HTML to a web page in react?',
        option1:'ReactDOM_render()',
        option2:'render()',
        option3:'render_DOM()',
        option4:'DOM_HTML()',
        answer:2,        
    },
    {
        question:'A state in React.js is also known as?',
        option1:'The internal storage of the component',
        option2:'External storage of the component',
        option3:'Permanent storage',
        option4:'All of the above',
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:'What are arbitrary inputs of components in react also known as?',
        option1:'Elements',
        option2:'Props',
        option3:'Keys',
        option4:'Ref',
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:'Using which of the following command can prevent default behaviour at in react?',
        option1:'preventDefault()',
        option2:'avoidDefault()',
        option3:'revokeDefault()',
        option4:'revokeDefault()',
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:'Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?',
        option1:'Virtual DOM',
        option2:'Original DOM',
        option3:'Both A and B',
        option4:'None of the above',
        answer:1,       
    },
    {
        question:'Which of the following method is used to access the state of a component from inside of a member function?',
        option1:'this.prototype.stateValue',
        option2:'this,getState()',
        option3:'this.values',
        option4:'this.state',
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:'Identify the smallest building block of React.JS.',
        option1:'Props',
        option2:'Elements',
        option3:'Components',
        option4:'None of the above',
        answer:3,
    }
]